Competition at its best!
Raising the Bar is a family, drama, tv movie film directed by Clay Glen.
16-year-old Kelly quits an elite gymnastics program and moves to Australia.
To help out a new friend and show up an old rival she re-enters competitive gymnastics,
she'll have to find a way to move forward while making amends with her past.
Kelly Johnson, played by Kelli Berglund.
Ashley, played by Emily Morris.
Teacher, played by Chris Koch.
Jordyn Wieber, played by Jordyn Wieber.
Judge, played by David John Clark.
Sarah Johnson, played by Peta Shannon.
Raising the Bar is a 2016 documentary film that follows six young individuals with Down syndrome from Australia
and India who perform a dance routine at the World Down Syndrome Congress 2015 in Chennai, India.
The film is directed by Onir and co-produced by Mitu Bhowmick Lange
and e.motion21, a non-profit Australian organisation.
The film won the Best Documentary award at the
Melbourne City Independent Film Awards 2018.
It was part of the official selection at the Maryland International Film
Festival 2017 and the Ethan Saylor Memorial Film Festival 2017.
The film explores themes of sports, gymnastics, gymnast.
The tone is emotional.